Now, with the decoy route again.
This opens up so many other things, so what the receiver has to do is he's gotta make sure--and we've gone over this before--that his initial steps look like he's getting the ball every time.
It's not just a matter of which route he's running but just the fact that he's even running a route.
So, Chris, we're going to explode out into the five yard stop.
And he's gotta force Brian to still make that decision and to back off of him; he doesn't want him to get too close.
This is where he can sit and open up.
Now that opens up many things for any other plays or players on the field.
This might be a running play, but he's got to run his route, essentially, just like the play before when he did get the ball.
So this time let's fire it out in full speed.
Set, go!
There you go.
It forces him to make a decision; meanwhile, the ball may be going someplace else.
But what he's done is he's locked in his defender's attention and caused him to not be able to read and react to anything else going on in the field.
He has to respect that this man can possibly get the ball and get down the field.